you wanted me here I am
i wanted to see what you do [ __ ]
and you didn't disappoint you let five
people die
then you let den take your place and
[ __ ]
even drag me that's cold well then
those muffles want you gone so things
can go back to the way they were
[ __ ] but I know the truth there's no
going back
you've changed things forever
[Laughter]
i don't want to kill you what would I be
doing without you ripping off my deals
no no no no no
you you complete me
[ __ ] average kill for money don't talk
like one of them you're not
even if you like to be
to them you're just a freak like me
they need you right now when they don't
they'll cast you out
see their mouth they're cold
it's a bad joke dropped at the first
sight of trouble
they're only as good as it will allow
them to be i'll show you
when the chips are down these uh
civilized
people they'll eat each other
see I'm not a monster
I'm just ahead of the cub damn yeah oh
[ __ ]
resident you have all these rules you
think they'll save you
ah everyone wrong that's the one rule
you have to break to know the truth
which is the only sensitive way to live
in this world is without rules
and tonight you're
no no
where are they killings making a troll
mountain
you have nothing nothing to slam me with
batman
you have nothing to do with all your
strength
get down [ __ ]